

Contact

19gures97@gmail.com

+48 782 160 301

https://www.linkedin.com/ in/marcin-gorecki-dev/

Skills

Languages: C/C++, Python

Version control systems (GIT SVN)

OS's RTOS, Linux, Windows

SEP 1kV

Team management

JIRA Confluence

Agile, Scrum, CI/CD, Docker

Languages

English C1

Spanish Al

Marcin Górecki

EMBEDDED DEVELOPER

About me

Embedded Developer with 5 years of experience in embedded development. Has experience with creating and maintaining controllers for HVAC and Automotive industries. Open for development in any embedded industries.

Has knowledge in C language, electronics, has experience with C#, knows Python, batch, bash and Powershell.

Passionate about operating systems and computer technology in general.

Experience

Embedded Software Engineer

SII SP Z O.O., BIAŁYSTOK

2023.01 - 2023.12(1 year)

- Developing and testing software for various hardwares with Atmega and STM32 microcontrollers
- Configuring and developing functions for FreeRTOS
- Configuring CI/CD for small projects in GitLab
- Managing a low-level part (C embedded/electronics) of a demonstration project

Junior Embedded Software Developer

PLUM SP. Z O.O., IGNATKI

2019.01-2022.12(4 years)

- Development and testing of software for custom hardware devices used in HVAC industry
- Development of software for production and troubleshooting support
- Development of software for automatic testing of algorithms.

Education

(2016-2020)Computer science, Bachelor

POLITECHNIKA BIAŁOSTOCKA, BIAŁYSTOK